{
    "id": "4e2d97aa4de7430abe4aaf34b5aef38b",
    "title": "Would vs. Should",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Mary ………………………….. arrive soon. She left office at",
            "description": "We use should to indicate possibility.",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9a46fbbabadb4b0c8c3d0c01e5d561e8"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. we ask for help?",
            "description": "We use should to ask for a suggestion.",
            "answers": [
                "Should",
                "Would"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7035b90989284854b3a14cd4f0e848bf"
        },
        {
            "question": "He …………………………. be acquitted.",
            "description": "We use should to express necessity.",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8632d2ecb0854e118e082241a9630ed4"
        },
        {
            "question": "People …………………….. obey the law.",
            "description": "We use should to express necessity.",
            "answers": [
                "should",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "af8b272ec16e490982afc6c577aae51a"
        },
        {
            "question": "You …………………………… done this to me.",
            "description": "Should have + past participle is used to criticize people for doing or not doing things.",
            "answers": [
                "wouldn't have",
                "shouldn't have"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9f7a83578bff453db6166caca583cb5f"
        },
        {
            "question": "He …………………………. wake up early if there was a good reason to.",
            "description": "In the second conditional, we use a past tense in the if-clause and would + infinitive in the main clause.",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ac7e93bd15ef4ad9aa2a2e1678c0f936"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………………. be grateful if you could help me.",
            "description": "Both would and should can be used with the first person pronouns with little difference of meaning.",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e8b4c67425604d659784c475e6f63a47"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………………. you like something to drink?",
            "description": "We use would in polite offers and requests.",
            "answers": [
                "Would",
                "Should"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fccd7016ab2d4f4ab88b72bf373a5aff"
        },
        {
            "question": "You …………………………. get that mole examined.",
            "description": "Should shows necessity or obligation. ",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "08c4a85ce2bc4ffe82ccfb472e533245"
        },
        {
            "question": "You ……………………………… apologize to him for behaving like that.",
            "description": "Should shows necessity or obligation. ",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "51e3c0a37a2c4eefb82dd43c6d1a9160"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………………. have wished him on his birthday, but I forgot.",
            "description": "Should have + past participle is used to criticize people for doing or not doing things.",
            "answers": [
                "should",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "16b633dcdd64439f9cd2b2a29100bc21"
        },
        {
            "question": "You ……………………………. have behaved like that.",
            "description": "Should have + past participle is used to criticize people for doing or not doing things.Should have + past participle is used to criticize people for doing or not doing things.",
            "answers": [
                "would not",
                "should not"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "920f841645fb46f8b88369f8f8a08392"
        }
    ]
}